# John Fry

(760) 470 - 8222 jfry@deadlowindustries.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/johnfry8

### Content Creator and AVMP student

High stress environment specialist, able to read and interpret advanced information and implement strategies accordingly. Volunteered for multiple fire departments. Able to actively listen during high stress moments. Held multiple leadership positions. Trained new employees to company and state protocols. Worked with multiple partners to oversee positive outcomes against all situations. Comfortable working with many different types of people and able to handle multiple projects while ensuring total accuracy.

## **Experience**

Podcast host and Content Creator, Mind Over Motor - Baltimore, MD June 2022 - Present

Create a podcast to explore therapeutic car building

- Interview individuals about their passion and why it helps them
- Write, record, edit and publish episodes (25 episodes)

Emergency Medical Technician - Central PA Region February 2011 - 2021

- Provided emergency medicine to the community
- Maintained State and National Licensure
- Worked within State and National protocols
- Trained new EMTs

United States Marine Corps, San Diego, CA 2007

• Private First Class

#### Education

Howard Community College Columbia, MD Audio, Video, Media Production AA Candidate 2023 - Current

HACC Shumaker Public Safety Center Harrisburg, PA EMT Program 2011 graduate, Class 18-72-069 Southern New Hampshire University Manchester, NH Marketing 2015 - 2017

#### **SKILLS**

- · Adobe Audition
- Adobe Premier Pro

References provided upon request

• Fluent in American Sign Language